A Guide to the Papers of James J. Kilpatrick
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series I: Correspondence
  - 1956-1966 Correspondence - Bri (Box-folder 5:4)
    Sen. John W. Bricker, Pauline Brickman, Harry Bridge, J. Ivey Bridgers-The Fidelity and Casualty Company of New York, Howard D. Bridges Jr., J. Malcolm Bridges-Richmond Chamber of Commerce, W.C. Bridges, Edna Briggs, Frank P. Briggs- The Daily Eagle, Jo Briggs, John Briggs- New York Times, Roger Briggs, William A. Briggs, John W. Bright-U.S. Department of the Interior, Robert Bright, Albert Brill, Edmond H. Brill Jr.-Richmond Chamber of Commerce, Mrs. Robert Bruce Brinsmade, Anna L. Brinton, C.W.L. Briscoe, J.C. Bristow-Home Life Insurance Company of New York, R.S. Bristow Jr., Aubrey Singer-British Broadcasting Corporation, Mrs. J.E. (McTrudie Bryant) Britt, Bessie S. Britton, Beverly L. Britton-A.H. Robins Company, R.T. Britton-Henrico County Public Schools, Darrel D. Brittsan-Sigma Phi Epsilon, Ellen B. Britzius
  - 1956-1966 Correspondence: Bro - Brown (Box-folder 5:5)
    J.P. Broaddus, R. Keith Broaders-American Book Company, Dr. J. Pelham Broadus D.D.S., Robert Deal Broadus-Kingsman Press, Rep. Bill Brock, Delia Brock-Blue Ridge Sanatorium, Mrs. Robert H. Broh-Kahn, Ruby B. Brooke, Mrs. N.W. Brooker, S.E. Brookings - Southern Railway Company, George Brooks-Larus and Brother Company Tobacco Manufacturers, George T. Broski, D.C. Brothers O.D., Ann H. Brown, Mrs. Bestor Brown, Bob Brown, C.K. Brown, L. Chauncey Brown, Clark Brown Jr., Delbert F. Brown, Donald W. Brown, Earl E. Brown - U.S. Department of Justice, Mrs. Constantine (Elizabeth Churchill) Brown, Fitzhugh L. Brown, Frank E. Brown, G.E. Brown-Natural Chimneys, Helen Brown, Helen H. Brown, James H. Brown, J.P. Brown - Pearl Laundry Company, John W. Brown-Lt. Governor of Ohio, Jonathan Brown- Danbury News-Times, Leonard S. Brown, Lewis D. Brown, Louis M. Brown, Paul V. Brown, Peggy (Mrs. Cabot) Brown, Robert Brown-WRVA-TV, Robert A. Brown, Robert C. Brown-Lee County Democratic Executive Committee, Rev. Robert R. Brown, Sandie Brown, Sterling W. Brown-National Conference of Christians and Jews, Viola J. Brown-American Foundation for the Blind, William B. Brown
  - 1956-1966 Correspondence: Browne - Bru (Box-folder 5:6)
    Fred Z. Browne, Millard Browne- Buffalo Evening News, Roy E. Brownell, Ida Jane Browner, Grant Browning, George Brownlee Jr.-Sandtown Civic Club, H.C. Brownson, Joel T. Broyhill, Mary Murphy Broyles, Matthew Bruccoli-University of Virginia Department of English, Donald C. Bruce-American Conservative Union, Jack Bruce-State ABC Board, Robert E. Bruce, Herbert Brucker- The Hartford Courant, Mrs. L.A. Brugh, Les Brumfield- The Clarion-Ledger, R.H. Bruni - Naturalized Citizens of America, Genevieve Brunson
  - 1959-1966 Correspondence: Allan C. Brownfeld (Box-folder 5:7)
  - 1948-1966 Correspondence - Bry (Box-folder 6:1)
    D. Tennant Bryan, Joe Bryan III, Stewart Bryan, Thomas P. Bryan - Mayor of Richmond, Mr. ___ Bryan, Chester Bryant, Rep. Farris Bryant -Florida House of Representatives, John C. Bryant, Linwood Bryant, Tidewater Bryant, Vaughn M. Bryant-Port of Houston, Victor S. Bryant, Vivian R. Bryant, William Clyde Bryant, William H. Bryant Jr., Dr. E.C. Bryce, Rev. G. MacLaren Brydon, Albert E. Bryson
  - 1956-1967 Correspondence: Buc - Burh (Box-folder 6:2)
    Bryan D. Buchanan, F.W. Buchanan, G.A. Buchanan- The Columbia Record, Mrs. H.S. Buchanan, J. Leo Buchanan, James Buchanan-Thomas Jefferson Center for Studies in Political Economy-University of Virginia, Art Buchwald Column, Walter A. Buchanan, Mrs. Clyve Buck, Dr. J.L. Blair Buck, Robert E. Buck-SDX, W.H. Buck, Walter H. Buck, F.R. Buckley, Reid Buckley, Maureen L. Buckley, George Walker Buckner- World Call, Elisabeth S. Bucock, Nelson H. Budd-National Canners Association, Harry Budge, A.O. Budina, Frederick Buechner, Ed Buford, Robert P. Buford, James L. Bugg Jr. - University of Missouri, E.D. Buie, Robert E. Bullard, Dana Bullen - Washington Evening Star- Sunday Star, Edgar S. Bundy-National Latman's Council Church League of America, William L. Bunting Jr. Virginia Law Weekly, Dr. Joseph Bunzel-National Association of Social Workers, William M. Burdette Jr., Roland E. Burdick-American Book Publishers Council, Bureau of National Affairs, Bureau of Property Records and Insurance, Mary-Lou Burelle, L. Burger, Judge Warren E. Burger, Austin Earle Burges, Aubrey L. Burgess, Massie C. Burgess, Col. Bob Burhans - Headquarters 80 th Division (Training)
  - 1956-1966 Correspondence: William F. Buckley Jr. (1925-2008) (Box-folder 6:3)
  - 1956-1966 Correspondence: Burk - Bux (Box-folder 6:4)
    Arthur W. Burke, Claire Burke, Ed Burke, Nathaniel Burke, R.F. Burke III-Crest Insurance Agency, Mrs. William W. Burke, Charles R. Burnett, W.G. Burnette, Clarence C. Burns, D.C. (Mrs. H.M.) Burns, James T. Burns, M.C. Burns, R.L. Burns, Charles A. Burnside, Jack E. Burnstein-U.S.S. Ticonderoga (CVA-14), John Shepard Burr University of Virginia Student Legal Forum, Mrs. Walter P. Burrier, R.H. Burroughs-Pittsburgh Plate Glass Company, Eleanor Burruss - St. Catherine's School, R.S. Burruss Jr., Mrs. A.L. Burton, Dave Burton, Herbert R. Burton, Larry L. Burton-Mountain State Christian High School, Susie Burton, Wynn Burton, Mrs. I.M. Bussells, Garland L. Busser, Jane Watson Bustard, M. Eugene Bustard, Adrian Bustilo-Swann Products, Lee Butcher, Mrs. Lillian Butcher, A.E. Butler, Alfred Butler, Alonzo E. Butler, Ernest L. Butler - Staunton-Augusta County Chamber of Commerce, Mrs. Ernest M. Butler Jr. Mrs. S.M. Butler Jr., Pick Butler-Virginia Farm Bureau Federation, W.P. Butler, Judge Thomas F. Butt, Sen. Jack H. Butterick, Robert Y. Button, H.L. Buurman-Information Service of South Africa, R. Buxley Sr.
  - 1956-1965 Correspondence - By (Box-folder 6:5)
    Ken Byerly Jr. Tidewater News, James K. Byers, Mrs. Howard T. Byles, Col. Hartwell T. Bynum, Ralph E. Byrd, Joseph Byrne, Frank T. Byrnes-Byrnes Bookkeeping Service, Gov. James F. Byrnes, Robert B. Byrnes, C.F. Byrns- Southwest American
  - 1949-1953 Correspondence: Senator Harry F. Byrd, Sr. (Box-folder 7:1)
  - 1954-1956 Correspondence: Senator Harry F. Byrd, Sr. (Box-folder 7:2)
  - 1957 Correspondence: Senator Harry F. Byrd, Sr. (Box-folder 7:3)
  - 1951-1964 Correspondence: Harry F. Byrd, Jr. (Box-folder 7:4)
  - 1956- 1967 Correspondence: C- Camm (Box-folder 7:5)
    Ann Perkins Cabell, Kathleen Cabell, P.A. Cabell, R. Baird Cabell, Roy E. Cabell, Douglas Caddy, Edward Caffery, Joe B. Cain Jr., Mary D. Cain- Congress of Freedom Inc., Stith M. Cain, Elizabeth Caldwell, George H. Caldwell, Katherine H. Caldwell, Mark B. Caldwell, Millard F. Caldwell- Supreme Court of Florida, William J. Caldwell- International Cooperation Administration, Paul Cales, Allston D. Calhoun Jr.-Americanism Preferred Devoted to the Advancement of Americanism, California- State Commissioner of Health, Eleanor Calkins, Frances S. Calkins- Public Schools of the City of Richmond, Alston Callahan, W.J. Callahan- U.S. Post Office Department Mail Frauds Investigations, Robert F. Cambell- Winston-Salem Journal, Twin City Sentinel, Cambridge University Press, Richmond Camellia Society, Camera Club of Richmond, Robert Cameron, J.W. Cammack
  - 1954-1965 Correspondence: Camp-Campb (Box-folder 7:6)
    J.L. Camp Jr.-Union Bag-Camp Paper Corporation, William M. Camp, Jameson G. Campaigne Jr. The Indianapolis Star, A.P. Campbell- Shenandoah Valley Electric Cooperative, Bruce Campbell- The Daily Plainsman, Hugh Campbell, Jewett Campbell, Mrs. Joseph Richard Campbell, Joseph S. Campbell, L.D. Campbell Sr., Leslie D. Campbell, Mrs. Leslie D. Campbell, Noreen Dickson Campbell, Robert F. Campbell Winston-Salem Journal-Sentinel, Taylor F. Campbell- Religious Goods Shop, W. Glenn Campbell- The Hoover Institution on War, Revolution, and Peace, W.P. Campbell- National Education Program
  - 1957-1967 Correspondence: Campe-Cann (Box-folder 7:7)
    John S. Campen, Andres N. Canales, Cancer Society, Arnold Canell, Gary Canion, Ralph Jerome Cannaday, Edmond W. Cannon, Thomas Cannon
  - 1949- 1966 Correspondence -Cano - Carg (Box-folder 8:1)
    Alfred O. Canon- Southwestern at Memphis, Rusty Cantelli, Edward Capers, Mortimer Caplin- U.S. Treasury Department, Capri Resident, Michael R. Caprio Jr-Phi Alpha Delta Law Fraternity, Charles M. Caravati, C.E. Carden, Philip M. Carden, Roscoe Carden, Edward S. Cardozo, Lewis Carey, Walter C. Carey, James Nelson Cargill- Cargill, Wilson and Acree Inc. Advertising
  - 1956-1965 Correspondence: Carh- Carp (Box-folder 8:2)
    William B. Carhart, William Edward Carle, Dixie Lee Carlson, D.K. Carlson, E. Tucker Carlton, H. Brannock Carlton, J.T. Carlton, Joseph D. Carlyle, Mark W. Carmen, Peter A. Carmichael- Louisiana State University Department of Philosophy, Marvin K. Carneale, Russell M. Carneal- Virginia House of Delegates, Charles E. Carney, E. Byrd Carnohan III, Joan Kelly Carolyn, J. Edward Carothers- Commission on the Church and Economic Life, National Council of the Churches of Christ in the USA, Neil Carothers, Clifford E. Carpenter- The Rochester Democrat and Chronicle, C.R. Carpenter- C.R. Carpenter & Co. Inc., Margaret Carpenter, Ethel Carpenter, J. Walter Carpenter, Keith B. Carpenter, Nancy L. Carper
  - 1956-1966 Correspondence: Carr-Carter (Box-folder 8:3)
    Arthur H. Carr, Roy A. Carr, Roy E. Carr, M.M. Carraway, Wilson Carraway- Tallahassee Bank and Trust Co., Frank E. Carrel Jr., Charles A. Carrico- D.C. Public School Administration, Henry L. Carroll, Mollie Ray Carroll, W.S. Carroll, John Jay Carson- Chris H. Whiteman and Associates, Mildred Carson- Lt. Commander International Naval Review Office, M.S. Carson- Naval Review Information Bureau, Nan Weller Carson- Rock Hill Public Library, R.B. Carson, J.G. Carswell- Sperry Piedmont Company, ___ Carter, Beryl T. Carter, Carlton Carter, Charles K. Carter Jr., Charles W. Carter, Miss Clyde Gregory Carter, E.B. Carter, Eloise D. Carter, Francis Edward Carter, G. Benjamin Carter- Department of Public Welfare, H. Carter, Lucile Carter- Virginia Division United Daughters of the Confederacy, Mann L. Carter, R.K. Carter, Mrs. William J. Carter- Hollins College Press Relations
  - 1947-1966 Correspondence: Carto-Cass (Box-folder 8:4)
    Willis A. Carto, Cartoon- On Parking Richmond News Leader, Howard H. Carwile, Violet Carwile, Clarence C. Case- Camp Roosevelt, Ralph D. Casey- University of Minnesota School of Journalism, Mrs. Richard T. Cash, W.M. Caskey- Mississippi College, Victor M. Cassidy
  - 1958-1966 Correspondence: Cast-Catledege (Box-folder 8:5)
    M.C. Caster, C.A. Castle, Louise Decatur Castleden- Ponce de Leon Hotel, Mitchell D. Cates, Thomas W. Cates, Mrs. Brawner Cates Jr., Catholic Press- Fordham University, Turner Catledge- New York Times
  - 1958-1966 Jamie Catterall-Valentine Museum, R.T. Catterall, Ralph Catteral, Mrs. Ralph Catterall, Bruce Catton, John Paul Causey, Ernest Cawcroft, Caxton Printers Ltd. (Box-folder 8:6)
  - 1953-1966 Correspondence: CB-Chap (Box-folder 8:7)
    CBS News, Richard P. Cecil- Whitney Communications Corporation, Anthony J. Celebrezze- Secretary of Health, Education, and Welfare, Central Richmond Association, Bennett Cerf- Random House, H.L. Chalfonte, Mrs. Clinton R. Chalkley, Mrs. M.R. Chalkley, Allan Knight Chalmers- NAACP Treasurer, Chamber of Commerce- Louisville, GA, Ann Chamberlain, Eli L. Chamberlain, John Chamberlain, Park Chamberlain, William D. Chamberlain- Charleston Evening Post, Lenoir Chambers- Virginian-Pilot, Bill Chambless- Minutes, Franklin Ross Chancey, Alfred D. Chandler, Connie L. Chandler, Dorothy E. Chandler, Richard A. Chandler- Assessor of Real Estate Richmond, Virginia W. Chapin, Mrs. George A. Chaplin, Mrs. ___ Chapman, C.L. Chapman, D.V. Chapman Jr.-Bureau of Engineering and Maintenance, Emeline P. Chapman, Jno. G. Chapman, John S. Chapman Jr.-The Virginians, Kenneth Chapman, Renda Chapman, Virginia Chapman, W. Frank Chapman- Town Manager Salem, VA, William Chapman, Willis Holmes Chapman
  - 1956-1966 Correspondence: Char-William P. Cheshire (Box-folder 9:1)
    Susan Charles, Charleston, SC, Charleston Gazette, Carol Charlton, Clarence R. Chase- Richmond Chamber Music Society, Dennis Chase, Derwood S. Chase Jr. - Investment Counsel Inc., Joan Charfield-Taylor- Smith College, Bruce D. Cheadle, H.S. Cheadle, Sgt. Dick Cheathan, Leslie Cheek Jr., Mrs. Leslie Cheek Jr.-Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, Rev. D.S. Cheetham, Brainard Cheney, Robert A. Chermside, Leo Cherne- Research Institute of America Inc., J.R. Cherry Jr., Kenneth J. Cherry, Chesapeake and Potomac Telephone Companies, Albert E. Chesham- Salvation Army, William P. Cheshire
  - 1956-1966 Correspondence - William P. Cheshire-Chod (Box-folder 9:2)
    William P. Cheshire, Ellen V. Chesley, H.G. Chesley Jr.-Wilson Paper Box Company, W.C. Chewning- Chewning and Smith Realtors, Chief Librarian- Cincinnati Public Library, Ralph Sutherland Child- Public Utilities Fortnightly, C.M. Childress, Clydean O. Childress, Mike Childress, E. Warren Chilton, W.R. Chilton- Shell Petroleum Products, China Film, Chinese News Service, Daisy Connell Chinn, Walter Chinn, J.J. Chiocca, Mrs. Charles F. Chipman, Mrs. Irene H. Chipman, Evelyn F. Chittum, Mrs. J.W. Chlubna, Frank Chodorov
  - 1952-1965 Correspondence - Chor-Ci (Box-folder 9:3)
    Kenneth Chorley, Carroll C. Chowning, L.N. Christensen- Kemper Insurance Company, Christian, Barton, Parker, and Boyd, E.A. Christian- Louisa County Board of Supervisors, George Christian, H.H. Christian, Jerry Eugene Christian- Southside State Farm, Malcolm M. Christian- Cutchins, Wallinger, Christian, and Wilkinson, Christian Science Publishing Society, Muriel B. Christison, John Christman, Christine Chrystal, Randolph W. Church- Virginia State Library, S.B. Churchill, Winston G. Churchill, Christian V. Cimmino- Mary Washington Hospital, Mrs. Elise Cimmino, Dennis Cipriano, Alton B. Cissell- Columbian Iron Works, Inc.,Citizens Council of America, City Plan Commission, Civil Rights Act, Civil Service Commission, Civil War Centenniel- Richmond, Civil War Commission, Civitan Club
  - 1949-1966 Correspondence - Cl-Charles R. Clark (Box-folder 9:4)
    William H. Claflin, Mrs. Robert W. Claiborne- Valentine Museum, George C. Clanton- Mayor of Tappahannock, VA, Sara Ashton Clapham, Lyman W. Clardy- WCBS Radio, A.M. Clark, Adele Clark, Charles A. Clark, Charles R. Clark
  - 1954-1966 Correspondence: D.H. Clark-Clary (Box-folder 9:5)
    Admiral D.H. Clark- Virginia State Ports Authority, David O. Clark, E.W. Clark, F.A. Clark Jr.-Commissioner of Health, State Health Department, F.E. Clark, G. Glenwood Clark, Mrs. Hoet (?) Clark, Jim Clark, J.L. Clark, Joseph S. Clark- U.S. Senate, Josephine G. Clark, Mary Faith Clark, Norvon Clark- Southern Railway System, Philip M. Clark, Robert H. Clark, Mrs. Russell J. Clark, Mr. and Mrs. Vern W. Clark, W. Preston Clark, Arthur Clarke, James W. Clarke, John R. Clarke- Northern Virginia Bonding Company, J. Calvitt, Clarke, Jr. and Mrs. J. Calvitt Clarke, Jr.-Congress Committee Children Inc., Peter F. Clarke- Pittsburgh Press, Shelton Clarke, Beverley B. Clary
  - 1951-1966 Correspondence - Clas-Clu (Box-folder 9:6)
    H. George Classen, Classic Features- The Literary Journal, H.B. Clay, Jim Clay, Joseph Clay, Mrs. Jack Clayton, John A. Clayton- Care of American Express, Linwood Clayton, Allen Cleaton- Collier's National Weekly, C. W. Cleaton, William Cleaton- State Insurance Board, F. Edison Cleland, Robert R. Cleland Jr., Mrs. Walter Clement, Clyde C. Clements- Longwood College English Department, James A. Clendinen- Tampa Morning Tribune, Jim Clendinen, J.H. Clendinen, C.V. Clifton- U.S. Army Acting Chief of Information, Ruth Clindaniel, R.R. Clindaniel, Ethel G. Cline, John Cline- Washington Star, Evelyn C. Clingensmith, Mrs. Harvey Archer Clopton, Mark Clutter- Wichita Beacon
  - 1950-1967 Correspondence - Co-Charles F. Cole (Box-folder 9:7)
    R.H. Coase- Journal of Law and Economics, University of Chicago Law School, Albert Coates- University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill, Harriette Cobb, Tyn Cobb Jr., Virginia Cobbs, Robert L. Coburn, Coca-Cola Company, George M. Cochran, Rexmond Canning Cochraine, Russell H. Cochrane, William B. Cocke Jr.-Sussex County Clerk, Monroe F. Cockrell, Frances D. Cocktrell, Mrs. William Codd, Kenneth Sewell Coe, Fred Coffield, Burt Coffin, John Cogan, William R. Cogar, John M. Coghill, Mary B. Coghill- Valentine Museum, Linda Cohen- Anchor Books Publicity, M.E. Cohen, Harry L. Cohn, Mrs. Jacob S. Cohn, Willis E. Cohoon, Thelma Coke-Medical College of Virginia, M.A. Coker, Mickey M. Colbert, John H. Colburn- Wichita Eagle and Beacon, Betty Cole - Meet the Press Associate Producer, Charles Fletcher Cole and Lucy Davis Cole-American National Red Cross
  - 1953-1966 Correspondence - Charles F. Cole-Collier's Encyclopedia (Box-folder 10:1)
    Charles F. Cole, David W. Cole- Lander College, Fred C. Cole- Washington and Lee University, Frederick H. Cole- Freeman and Cole, H. Milton Cole Jr., Kathleen B. Cole, Mildred Cole, W.R. Cole Jr., Miles L. Colean, Audrey R. Coleman, E.C. Coleman- Long Manufacturing Company Inc., Claudius S. Coleman, H.C. Coleman, John Coleman, John S. Coleman- Veterans Administration Center, M. Coleman, Daniel Coley- North Carolina Prison Department, Mrs. Harvey L. Colgin, Chris Collan, Collegiate Schools, R.E. Coller- Allstate Insurance Company, David S. Collier- Executive Director Modern Age, Fred. C.D. Collier- University of Alabama Medical Center, Mark H. Collier- Legislative Council Committee, Collier's Encyclopedia
  - 1951-1966 Correspondence - Collier's Yearbook-Virginia Commission on Constitutional Government, Collier's Yearbook, Mrs. C.C. Collins, E.E. Collins, Honorable Lewis Preston-Lt. Governor of Virginia, Mary Love Collins, Ralph B. Collins, John Collison, Mrs. Rex Collins, Bertha Colon, James B. Colvin, George Hamilton Combs-American Broadcasting Company, William M. Comfort- Victory Baptist Church, Virginia Commission on Constitutional Government (Box-folder 10:2)
  - 1958-1959 Correspondence with Virginia Commission on Constitutional Government (Box-folder 10:3)
  - 1959-1962 Correspondence with Virginia Commission on Constitutional Government (Box-folder 10:4)
  - 1962 Correspondence with Virginia Commission on Constitutional Government (Box-folder 10:5)
  - 1957-1966 Correspondence: Virginia Commission on Constitutional Government-Con Virginia Commission on Constitutional Government, Communism Crusade, E.C. Compton, Mildred H. Conant, B.O. Cone- Crawford Manufacturing Company, Ceasar Cone- Cone Mills Corporation (Box-folder 10:6)
  - 1950-1965 Correspondence - Coner-Cony (Box-folder 10:7)
    William P. Conery- Southern Pine Association, Conference of Chief Justice, Virginia Congleton, Congress of United States- Committee on Foreign Affairs, Congress of United States- Committee on Interior and Insular Affairs, Congress of United States- District of Colombia, Congress of United States- Armed Services, Congress of United States- Un-American Activities, Congress of United States- Post Office and Civil Service, Congressional Hotel, Congressional Quarterly, Harrie Byrd Conlin, Mr. and Mrs. J. Connally, Bob Connell, Frank G. Connelly, Winfred Conner, Mrs. Larry Connor, Laurence R. Connor- Colombus Dispatch, Louis M. Connor Jr.-National Association of Manufacturers, Sherry Conohan, Edwin P. Conquest, Will C. Conrad- Milwaukee Journal, Constitution Party of the United States, Martha Conway- Secretary of Commonwealth, A.E. Conyers- Truck Drivers and Helpers Union
  - 1952-1966 Correspondence - Coo-Core (Box-folder 10:8)
    Charles B. Cook, Honorable Eugene Cook- Attorney General of Georgia, Mrs. J.D. Cook, John Randall Cook, M.L. Cook, Samuel D. Cook, Charles Cooke- American Guild of Organists, Edna Ellis Cooke, Forest W. Cooke- WHBF Radio 1270, James J. Cooke, Robert T. Cooke, C.W. Coons, Lucy O. Coons- Goucher College, Donald Cooper- All State Real Estate, Emzy Cooper, Gene L. Cooper, Herman A. Cooper, Trace H. Cooper, Weldon Cooper- UVA Newsletter, Millard Cope- Marshall News Messenger, Richard W. Copeland- Department of Welfare and Institutions, Robert J. Corber- Republican Party of Virginia, Warren Corbett- WRVU Radio, R.H. Cornell- Friends of Rhodesia Trust, Mrs. W.S. Corkran, J.D. Corcoran- Queens Chiropractic Group, John T. Core
  - 1952-1967 Correspondence: Corel-Couc (Box-folder 11:1)
    George N. Corelle, Anne Corley- Washington Admirals Club, Joseph M. Cormack- College of William and Mary School of Law, Katherine Cornett, Richard C. Cornuwelle- United Student Aid Fund, Philip L. Corson, John J. Cortopassi, Osmond F. Cosby, Henry M. Cosimini, Don Costa, John A. Costello, Robert E. Costello, T.R. Cotton, Walker Cottrell, William T. Couch- Collier's Encyclopedia
  - 1956-1966 Correspondence: Coug-Cous (Box-folder 11:2)
    Kevin Coughlin, R.P. Coughlin, Council for Basic Education, Council of State Governments, Council on Foreign Relations, Captain John M. Court, Kent Courtney, Mary T. Courtney, Phoebe Courtney- The Independent American, Conservative Society of America, Norman Cousins- The Saturday Review, R.J. Cousins
  - 1956-1965 Correspondence: Cov-Coz (Box-folder 11:3)
    F.W. Covert, N.W. Covington Jr.-Manufacturers Life Insurance Company, Mrs. T. Covan, Edward Cowan, J.B. Cowan, Walter G. Cowan, Henry M. Cowardin, Elizabeth S. Cowles, Porter Cowles- University of North Carolina Press, E. Van Dyke Cox Jr., Earl S. Cox- First Baptist Church, Edwin Cox- Virginia-Carolina Chemical Corporation, Elbert Cox- Department of the Interior, Elizabeth M. Cox, Fletcher Cox Jr.- Rural Virginia, Stephen Banner Cox, Walter Cox, Nelson Y. Coxe, Mary E. Coxon, Mrs. Herbert D. Coy- Elizabeth Kates Foundation, William B. Cozad
  - 1951-1966 Correspondence: Cr-Cran (Box-folder 11:4)
    Crafton and Sparks, Paul S. Cragan, Edna C. Craig, J.A. Craig Jr.- Magnolia Chamber of Congress, Jean Craig, May Craig, Nancy Craig, Paul F. Craig- Springfield Union, F.W. Craigie, Walter Craigie- F.W. Craigie & Company, Evelyn Crane, Frank H. Crane- Indianapolis Star, Joan S. Crane, John B. Crane, R.H. Crane
  - 1956-1966 Correspondence: Crav-Lucy Crockett (Box-folder 11:5)
    John Park Cravens, Mildred Crawbuck- North American Newspaper Alliance, Edwin M. McClure- McClure Newspaper Syndicate, Crawford Veterinary Hospital, Jerry Crawford- Wake Forest College, R.B. Crawford, Robert Crawford- Defenders of Independent Rights and State Sovereignty, W.M. Crawford, John O. Crawford, J.H. Creecy, Chester A. Creider, Creighton University, Colonel R.P. Crenshaw Jr.- The Anchorage, Miriam Crenshaw, Ruth T. Crenshaw- Belle Bryan Day Nursery, Terry Crenshaw, Richmond Crinkley- Graduate School of Arts and Sciences University of Virginia, Charlotte Crippen- United Daughters of the Confederacy, Crippled Children's Hospital, K.R. Crispell- Medicine at University of Virginia, Helen Jo Crissman- University of Missouri at Kansas City, Bessie L. Crocker, Lucy H. Crockett
  - 1950-1966 Correspondence: Paul Crockett-Crug (Box-folder 11:6)
    Paul Crockett- House of Delegates, Mrs. W. Hamilton Crockford III, Albert Croissant- Occidental College, Glenn P. Crone- Schmidt and Wilson, Towne and Country, Adele R. Cronin, Earle T. Cronk, Robert G. Cronson- Insurance City Life Company, C.A. Crooks, Kenneth W. Crosby- Juniata College, Neil V. Crosby, Charles B. Cross Jr., John W. Croswell, B.W. Crouch Jr., John W. Croswell, B.W. Crouch Jr., James E. Crow, Morrill M. Crowe, E.H. Crowson, Douglas W. Cruger- Andover Newton Theological School
  - 1951-1966 Correspondence: Crum-Crut (Box-folder 11:7)